[Music]
normally I don't give a shit about
current events so they don't really
affect me
this doesn't really affect me either but
your reaction does that's why they took
it too far
listen up I'm not scared of the
coronavirus I'm just scared to achieve
people arms I can't start a rebellion if
you people are like this see I'm still
going to work I'm still fine on planes
I'm still eating the restaurants now
we'll tell you their names sure it's sad
a lot of people might pass away but on
the planet I'm from people die every day
they kill the subcultures they cancel
the future and for what for you to not
be offended follow along and just wait
to get fucked - got a preserve life
preserve it for what they can't tell you
because they don't know will they ban a
young SoundCloud for this let's try
everybody take your masks off and go
outside and there's a one in a thousand
chance you might die but if you won't
take those odds than you're dead inside
[Music]